? (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS) ?
?(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)?
Who would you say is the father?
你会说谁是父亲?
You.
您。
I'm going to put a prince in your belly.
我要把王子放在你肚子里。
Our queen has a keen sense of poetic justice.
我们的女王有一种敏锐的诗意正义感。
What would she do for the man
她会为这个男人做些什么
who rids her of her treasonous brothers?
谁让她叛逆的兄弟?
JON SNOW: My name... my real name...
JON SNOW:我的名字...... 我的真名......
is Aegon Targaryen.
是Aegon Targaryen。
It's true, Dany.
这是真的，丹妮。
If it were true...
如果是真的......
you'd have a claim to the Iron Throne.
你有对铁王座的要求。
ARYA STARK: She doesn't like your queen, does she?
ARYA STARK:她不喜欢你的女王，是吗?
She's defending our family.
她在捍卫我们的家庭。
I'm her family, too.
我也是她的家人。
ARYA: Don't forget that.
阿亚:别忘了。
? (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ?
?(音乐强化)?
(LYANNA MORMONT GASPING)
(LYANNA MORMONT GASPING)
-(YELLS) -(GIANT WIGHT SHRIEKS)
- (大叫) - (GIANT WIGHT SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTING)
(叫声)
(DAENERYS TARGARYEN SOBBING)
(DAENERYS TARGARYEN SOBBING)
? (SOMBER MUSIC CONCLUDES) ?
?(SOMBER MUSIC CONCLUDES)?
JON: We're here to say goodbye to our brothers and sisters.
JON: 我们在这里向我们的兄弟姐妹道别。
To our fathers and mothers.
给我们的父亲和母亲。
To our friends.
给我们的朋友。
Our fellow men and women
我们的男女同胞
who set aside their differences...
谁抛开他们的分歧......
to fight together...
一起战斗......
and die together
和死在一起
so that others might live.
这样别人就可以活下去了。
Everyone in this world
这个世界上的每个人
owes them a debt that can never be repaid.
欠他们的是一笔永远无法偿还的债务。
It is our duty and our honor
这是我们的责任和荣誉
to keep them alive in memory...
让他们在记忆中活着......
for those who come after us...
对于那些追随我们的人......
and those who come after them...
那些追随他们的人......
for as long as men draw breath.
只要男人吸气。
They were the shields that guarded the realms of men.
他们是守卫人类王国的盾牌。
And we shall never see their like again.
我们永远不会再见到他们的样子。
MAN: To your health.
人: 为了您的健康。
Have you seen Arya?
你见过艾莉亚吗?
You can still smell the burning bodies,
你仍然可以闻到燃烧的身体，
and that's where your head is at.
那就是你的头脑所在。
-I just want to thank her for-- -I'm sure you do.
- 我只想感谢她 - - 我敢肯定你这样做。
Look, it's not about that.
看，这不是那个。
Of course it's about that, you twat.
当然是关于那个， 你傻了。
Why shouldn't it be?
为什么不应该呢?
The dead are dead. You're not.
死者已经死了。你不是。
Gendry.
Gendry。
That's right, isn't it?
那是对的，不是吗?
Yes, Your Grace.
是的，你的恩典。
You're Robert Baratheon's son.
你是Robert Baratheon的儿子。
You are aware he took my family's throne
你知道他带走了我家的宝座
and tried to have me murdered?
并试图让我谋杀?
I didn't even know he was my father until after he was dead.
在他去世之前我甚至不知道他是我的父亲。
Yes, he's dead.
是的，他死了。 他的兄弟也是。 那么现在谁是风暴之王? 我不知道，你的恩典。
Does anyone?
有没有人?
I think you should be Lord of Storm's End.
我想你应该成为风暴之王的终结。
I can't be. I'm a bastard.
我不能。我是个混蛋。
No, you are Lord Gendry Baratheon of Storm's End,
不，你是Storm's End的Gendry Baratheon勋爵，
the lawful son of Robert Baratheon.
Robert Baratheon的合法之子。
Because that is what I have made you.
因为那是我给你的。
To Lord Gendry Baratheon of Storm's End.
风暴之巅的Gendry Baratheon勋爵。
-To Gendry!
- 给Gendry！
MAN 1: Lord Gendry!
男人1: Gendry勋爵！
MAN 2: Gendry!
男人2: Gendry！
MAN 3: Gendry! MAN 4: Gendry!
男人3:Gendry！ 男人4:Gendry！
MAN 5: Lord Gendry!
男人5: Gendry勋爵！
MAN 6: Gendry!
男人6: Gendry！
MAN 7: That's easy, isn't it?
男人7: 这很容易，不是吗?
-A fitting reward for a hero. SAMWELL: Uh, hold on.
- 英雄的合适奖励。 SAMWELL:呃，坚持下去。
TYRION: And a Lord of Storm's End who will be forever loyal to you.
TYRION: 而风暴之王将会永远忠于你。
MAN 8: Come, my lord. -See?
男子8:来吧，我的主人。 -看到?
You're not the only one who's clever.
你不是唯一一个聪明的人。
WOMAN: I have to go down and get another barrel.
女人: 我得走下去再换一桶。
JAIME: We fought dead things and lived to talk about it.
JAIME: 我们为死去的东西而战，并且生活在谈论它。
If this isn't the time to drink, when is?
如果这不是喝酒的时间， 什么时候?
The last time I saw her,
我最后一次见到她，
I told her I'd kill her if I ever saw her again.
我告诉她，如果我再见到她，我会杀了她。
-I'm sure you had your reasons. -I did.
- 我相信你有理由。 - 我做到了。
-I do. -So did you?
-我做。 - 你呢?
Never got the chance.
永远不会有机会。
She did it to herself.
她自己做了。
Or her god did it to her.
或者她的上帝对她做了。
Lord of Light.
光明之王。
We play his game for him, we fight his war and win,
我们为他打比赛， 我们打他的战争赢了，
and then
然后
he fucks off.
他乱搞了。
No signs, no blessings. Who knows what he wants?
没有迹象，没有祝福。 谁知道他想要什么?
I don't imagine thinking about that subject
我没想到想到这个话题
will leave you any happier than before.
会让你比以前更快乐。
And what if I'm not trying to be happy?
如果我不想快乐怎么办?
Then you're in luck.
那你很幸运。
We may have defeated them,
我们可能打败了他们，
but we still have us to contend with.
但我们还是要让我们来应对。
Thank you. I feel much better.
谢谢。我感觉好多了。
MAN: More ale!
人: 更多啤酒！
This is clever.
这很聪明。
Even better than the saddle I designed for you.
甚至比我为你设计的马鞍还要好。
It's the same as the one Daeron Targaryen built
它和Daeron Targaryen建造的一样
for his crippled nephew 120 years ago.
对于120年前残废的侄子。
I liked that one.
我喜欢那个。
You know our history better than anyone.
你比任何人都更了解我们的历史。
That will be useful as Lord of Winterfell.
这将是Winterfell的主人。
I'm not Lord of Winterfell.
我不是温特费尔的主。
You're the only surviving trueborn son of Ned Stark.
你是Ned Stark唯一幸存的儿子。
You don't want it.
你不想要它。
I don't really want anymore.
我真的不想要了。
I envy you.
我羡慕你。
You shouldn't envy me.
你不应该羡慕我。
Mostly I live in the past.
我大多生活在过去。
TORMUND: All of it. -Go on.
TORMUND:全部。 -继续。
-No, not in one go. -Go on. I believe in you.
不，不是一气呵成。 -继续。我相信你。
TORMUND: We have to celebrate our victory.
TORMUND: 我们必须庆祝我们的胜利。
Vomiting is not celebrating.
呕吐不是在庆祝。
-Yes, it is.
-是的。
Ah!
啊!
To the Dragon Queen!
给龙女王！
To Arya Stark, the hero of Winterfell!
致Arya Stark， Winterfell的英雄！
-Rah! Rah! Rah! Rah! WOMAN: Drink!
-Rah！RAH！RAH！RAH！ 女人:喝！
TORMUND: I'm fine!
TORMUND: 我很好！
Your turn.
轮到你了。
Um...
嗯...
You are an only child.
你是独生子女。
-I told you I was. -You didn't.
我告诉过你我。 - 你没有。
-I did. -I surmised it.
- 我做到了。 - 我推测它。
Drink.
喝。
Go again.
再去一次。
Why does he get to go again?
他为什么要再去一次?
Because it's my game.
因为这是我的游戏。
You have danced with Renly Baratheon.
你和Renly Baratheon一起跳舞。
No.
没有。
TYRION: Drink.
TYRION: 喝。
MAN: The other way around!
人: 另一种方式！
I saw him riding that thing.
我看到他骑那个东西。
-We all did. -No. No.
- 我们都做到了。 -没有。没有。
I saw him riding that thing.
我看到他骑那个东西。
-That's right, you did. -I did.
- 那是对的，你做到了。 - 我做到了。
That's why we all agreed to follow him.
这就是我们都同意跟随他的原因。
That's the kind of man he is.
那是他的那种人。
He's little...
他很小......
...but he's strong.
......但他很强壮。
Strong enough to befriend an enemy
足以与敌人交朋友
and get murdered for it!
为此而被谋杀！
Most people get bloody murdered,
大多数人都被谋杀了，
they stay that way.
他们保持这种方式。
TORMUND: Not this one.
TORMUND:不是这个。
Yeah, I didn't have much say in that.
是啊， 我没有太多发言权。
Ah! He comes back and keeps fighting.
啊! 他回来继续战斗。
Here, north of the Wall, and then back here again.
在这里，在墙的北边， 然后再回到这里。
He keeps fighting.
他一直在战斗。
He climbed on a fucking dragon and fought.
他爬上了他妈的龙并且奋战了。
What kind of person climbs on a fucking dragon?
什么样的人爬上他妈的龙?
A madman or a king!
疯子还是国王！
TYRION: Drink. -Drink.
TYRION:喝。 -喝。
Drink.
喝。
Wrong!
错误！
Wrong, wrong, wrong! Drink!
错，错，错！喝！
Mm!
嗯！
You were married. Before Sansa.
你结婚了 在Sansa之前。
-Drink.
-喝。
You're drinking wine, but you prefer ale!
你在喝葡萄酒， 但你更喜欢啤酒！
No!
没有！
You're a virgin.
你是处女。
That's a statement about the present.
这是关于现在的陈述。
At no point in the past, up until this very moment,
在过去的任何时候， 直到这一刻，
have you slept with a man.
你和一个男人睡过了吗?
Or a woman.
还是女人
I have to piss.
我不得不小便。
We did it! We faced those icy fucks.
我们做到了！ 我们遇到了那些冰冷的乱搞。
Looked right into their blue eyes,
看着他们的蓝眼睛，
and here we are.
我们在这里。
Now, which one of you cowards shit in my pants?
现在，你们哪一个懦夫穿在我的裤子里?
Please pardon me for a moment.
请原谅我一下。
MAN: Drink it!
人: 喝吧！
And after all that,
毕竟，
this fucker comes north and takes her from me.
这个笨蛋来到北方，带她离开我。
Just takes her, like that.
就这样接受她。
I mean it, Clegane.
我的意思是，Clegane。
My heart is broken.
我的心碎了。
Don't touch me.
别碰我。
WILLA: You can touch me.
WILLA: 你可以碰我
I'm not afraid of wildlings.
我不怕野人。
Maybe you should be.
也许你应该。
Well, Clegane...
好吧，Clegane ......
it's time to drown our sorrows.
是时候淹没我们的悲伤了。
I'm not done with my drink.
我没喝完我的饮料。
MAN 2: You saved the day.
男子2:你救了这一天。
MAN 1: You owe me one.
男人1: 你欠我一次。
-Don't forget that. MAN 2: For the rest of my days.
- 别忘了。 男子2:剩下的日子。
Are you ready now?
准备好了吗?
This is my drink.
这是我的饮料。
All right!
行！
SANSA: She could have made you happy, for a little while.
SANSA: 她本可以让你开心， 一小会儿。
There's only one thing that'll make me happy.
只有一件事会让我开心。
And what's that?
那是什么?
That's my fucking business.
那是他妈的生意。
Used to be you couldn't look at me.
曾经是你无法看着我。
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前的事。
I've seen much worse than you since then.
从那以后，我见过比你更糟糕的事情。
HOUND: Yes, I've heard.
猎犬: 是的，我听说过。
Heard you were broken in.
听说你被打破了。
Heard you were broken in rough.
听说你粗暴地被打破了。
And he got what he deserved.
他得到了他应得的。
I gave it to him.
我把它给了他。
How?
怎么样?
Hounds.
猎犬。
You've changed, Little Bird.
你改变了，小鸟。
None of it would have happened
这一切都不会发生
if you'd left King's Landing with me.
如果你和我一起离开了King's Landing。
No Littlefinger, no Ramsay...
没有Littlefinger，没有Ramsay ......
none of it.
没有。
Without Littlefinger, and Ramsay and the rest,
没有Littlefinger， 和拉姆齐以及其他人，
I would have stayed a Little Bird all my life.
我一辈子都会留下一只小鸟。
MAN 1: Hey! MAN 2: Pour another one.
男人1:嘿！ 男子2:倒另一个。
Don't shoot.
不要开枪。
It's nighttime, it's freezing, and everyone's celebrating.
这是夜晚，它很冷， 每个人都在庆祝
You should be celebrating with them.
你应该和他们一起庆祝。
I am celebrating.
我在庆祝
Yeah, I am too.
是的，我也是。
I'm not Gendry Rivers anymore.
我不再是Gendry Rivers了。
I'm Gendry Baratheon, Lord of Storm's End.
我是Gendry Baratheon， 风暴之王的结局。
By order of the queen.
按照女王的命令。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
I don't know how to be lord of anything.
我不知道如何做任何事情。
I hardly know how to use a fork.
我几乎不知道怎么用叉子。
All I know is that you're beautiful,
我只知道你很漂亮
and I love you,
我爱你，
and none of it will be worth anything
并没有任何价值
if you're not with me.
如果你不跟我在一起
So be with me.
所以和我在一起吧。
Be my wife. Be the Lady of Storm's End.
做我的妻子。 成为风暴之巅的女士。
You'll be a wonderful lord,
你会成为一个美好的领主，
and any lady would be lucky to have you.
任何女士都很幸运能拥有你。
But I'm not a lady.
但我不是女士。
I never have been.
我从来没有过。
That's not me.
不是我。
You didn't drink.
你没有喝酒。
-I didn't drink? -In the game.
- 我不喝酒? -在游戏里。
-I drank. -In the game. This is Dornish.
我喝了 -在游戏里。这是Dornish。
This is not the game. This is only drinking.
这不是游戏。 这只是喝酒。
Suit yourself.
你自便。
You keep it warm enough in here.
你在这里保持足够的温暖。
It's the first thing I learnt when I came to the North.
这是我来北方时学到的第一件事。
Keep your fire going.
保持火势。
Every time you leave the room, put more wood on.
每次你离开房间， 把更多的木材放在上面
That's very diligent. Very responsible.
那非常勤奋。 非常负责任。
-Piss off. -You know the first thing
-生气。 - 你知道第一件事
I learned in the North?
我在北方学到了什么?
I hate the fucking North.
我恨他妈的北。
It grows on you.
它会在你身上发展。
I don't want things growing on me.
我不希望事情在我身上成长。
How about Tormund Giantsbane?
Tormund Giantsbane怎么样?
Has he grown on you?
他在你身上长大了吗?
You sound quite jealous.
你听起来很嫉妒。
I do, don't I?
我知道，不是吗?
It's bloody hot in here.
这里真是热闹。
Oh, move aside.
哦，搬到一边。
What are you doing?
你在做什么?
I'm taking your shirt off.
我脱掉你的衬衫。
I've never slept with a knight before.
我以前从未和骑士睡过。
I've never slept with anyone before.
我以前从未和任何人睡过。
Then you have to drink. Those are the rules.
然后你必须喝。 这些都是规则。
I told you--
我告诉你了 -
Are you drunk?
你醉了吗?
No.
没有。
Only a little.
只有一点。
I didn't know Ser Jorah well...
我不太了解Ser Jorah ......
but I know this.
但我知道这一点。
If he could have chosen a way to die,
如果他能选择一种死亡方式，
it would have been protecting you.
它会保护你。
He loved me.
他爱我。
And I couldn't love him back.
我无法爱他。
Not the way he wanted.
不是他想要的方式。
Not the way I love you.
不是我爱你的方式。
Is that all right?
那好吗?
I wish you'd never told me.
我希望你永远不会告诉我。
If I didn't know, I'd be happy right now.
如果我不知道， 我现在很高兴。
I try to forget.
我试着忘了。
Tonight I did for a while,
今晚我做了一会儿，
and then I saw them gathered around you.
然后我看到他们聚集在你身边。
I saw the way they looked at you.
我看到了他们看着你的方式。
I know that look.
我知道那个样子。
So many people have looked at me that way, but never here.
很多人都这样看着我，但从来没有在这里。
Never on this side of the sea.
永远不要在海的这一边。
I told you I don't want it.
我告诉过你我不想要它。
It doesn't matter what you want.
你想要什么并不重要。
You didn't want to be King in the North.
你不想成为北方的国王。
What happens when they demand you press your claim,
当他们要求您按下您的索赔时会发生什么
and take what is mine?
拿走我的是什么?
I'll refuse.
我会拒绝
You are my queen. I don't know what else I can say.
你是我的女王。我不知道还能说些什么。
You can say nothing.
你什么都不说。
To anyone, ever.
任何人，永远。
Never tell them who you really are.
永远不要告诉他们你到底是谁。
Swear your brother and Samwell Tarly to secrecy,
发誓你的兄弟和Samwell Tarly要保密，
and tell no one else.
并告诉别人。
Or it will take on a life of its own
或者它会带来自己的生命
and you won't be able to control it
你将无法控制它
or what it does to people.
或者它对人们做了什么。
No matter how many times you bend the knee,
无论你弯曲膝盖多少次，
no matter what you swear.
无论你发誓什么。
I want it to be the way it was between us.
我希望它成为我们之间的方式。
I have to tell Sansa and Arya.
我必须告诉Sansa和Arya。
Sansa will want to see me gone and you on the Iron Throne.
Sansa希望看到我和你走在铁王座上。
She won't.
她不会。
She's not the girl you grew up with.
她不是你长大的女孩。
Not after what she's seen,
不是在她看到之后，
not after what they've done to her.
不是在他们对她做了什么之后。
I owe them the truth.
我欠他们真相。
Even if the truth destroys us?
即使真相摧毁了我们?
-It won't. -It will.
- 不会。 -它会。
I've never begged for anything...
我从来没有求过任何事......
but I'm begging you.
但我求求你
Don't do this. Please.
不要这样做。请。
You are my queen.
你是我的女王。
Nothing will change that.
什么都不会改变。
And they are my family.
他们是我的家人。
We can live together.
我们可以共同生活。
We can.
我们可以。
I've just told you how.
我刚刚告诉你怎么样。
Half are gone.
一半都没了。
The Northmen as well.
北方人也是。
And the Golden Company has arrived in King's Landing,
黄金公司已抵达国王登陆，
courtesy of the Greyjoy fleet.
礼貌的Greyjoy舰队。
The balance has grown distressingly even.
平衡甚至令人沮丧。
When the people find out what we have done for them,
当人们发现我们为他们做了什么，
that we saved them--
我们拯救了他们 -
Cersei will make sure they don't believe it.
瑟曦将确保他们不相信。
We will hit her hard.
我们会努力的。
We will rip her out root and stem.
我们会把她扯掉根茎。
The objective here is to remove Cersei
这里的目标是删除Cersei
without destroying King's Landing.
没有摧毁国王的着陆。
VARYS: Thankfully, she's losing allies by the day.
瓦里斯: 值得庆幸的是，她在白天失去了盟友。
Yara Greyjoy has retaken the Iron Islands
Yara Greyjoy重新夺回了Iron Islands
in her queen's name.
用她女王的名字。
The new Prince of Dorne pledges his support.
新的多恩王子承诺支持他。
No matter how many lords turn against her,
无论有多少领主反对她，
as long as she sits on the Iron Throne,
只要她坐在铁王座上，
she can call herself Queen of the Seven Kingdoms.
她可以称自己为七国女王。
We need the capital.
我们需要资本。
I watched the people of King's Landing
我看着King's Landing的人
rebel against their king when they were hungry,
他们饿的时候反抗他们的国王，
and that was before winter began.
那是在冬天来临之前。
Give them the opportunity and they will cast Cersei aside.
给他们机会，他们会把Cersei抛到一边。
JON: We'll surround the city.
JON: 我们将围绕这座城市。
If the Iron Fleet tries to ferry in more food,
如果铁舰队试图运送更多的食物，
the dragons will destroy them.
龙将摧毁它们。
If the Lannisters and the Golden Company attack,
如果Lannisters和Golden Company发起攻击，
we'll defeat them in the field.
我们会在战场上打败他们。
Once the people see that Cersei is our only enemy,
一旦人们看到瑟曦是我们唯一的敌人，
her reign is over.
她的统治结束了。
All right.
行。
SANSA: The men we have left are exhausted.
SANSA: 我们离开的人都筋疲力尽了。
Many of them are wounded.
其中许多人受伤。
They'll fight better if they have time
如果他们有时间，他们会更好地战斗
to rest and recuperate.
休息和恢复。
How long do you suggest?
你建议多久了?
SANSA: I can't say for certain,
SANSA: 我不能肯定地说，
not without talking to the officers.
不是没有与官员交谈。
I came north to fight alongside you
我来到北方与你并肩作战
at great cost to my armies and myself.
对我的军队和我自己造成巨大损失。
Now that the time has come to reciprocate,
现在是时候回首了，
you want to postpone.
你想推迟。
It's not just our people. It's yours.
这不仅仅是我们的员工。 是你的。
You want to throw them into a war
你想把他们扔进战争
they're not ready to fight?
他们还没有准备好战斗?
The longer I leave my enemies alone,
我离开敌人的时间越长，
the stronger they become.
他们变得越强大。
The Northern forces will honor their promises
北方军队将兑现他们的承诺
and their allegiance
和他们的效忠
to the Queen of the Seven Kingdoms.
七国女王。
What you command, we will obey.
你的命令，我们会服从。
TYRION: So...
TYRION: 所以...
if all are in agreement...
如果所有人都同意......
Jon and Ser Davos will ride down the Kingsroad
Jon和Ser Davos将乘坐Kingsroad
with the Northern troops
与北方军队
and the bulk of the remaining Dothraki and Unsullied.
剩下的Dothraki和Unsullied的大部分。
A smaller group of us will ride to White Harbor,
我们中的一小部分人将乘车前往白港，
and sail from there to Dragonstone
从那里驶向龙石
with our queen and her dragons accompanying us from above.
我们的女王和她的龙从上面陪伴着我们。
Ser Jaime has chosen to remain here,
Ser Jaime选择留在这里，
as a guest of the Lady of Winterfell.
作为Winterfell夫人的客人。
We have won the Great War.
我们赢得了伟大的战争。
Now we will win the Last War.
现在我们将赢得最后的战争。
In all Seven Kingdoms,
在所有七国中，
men will live without fear and cruelty
男人将生活得没有恐惧和残忍
under their rightful queen.
在他们的合法女王之下。
We need a word.
我们需要一个词。
You understand we'd all be dead if not for her.
你知道，如果不是她，我们都会死。
We'd be corpses marching down to King's Landing.
我们将军队前往国王登陆。
Arya's the one that killed the Night King.
艾莉亚是那个杀死夜王的人。
Her men gave their lives defending Winterfell--
她的手下为Winterfell辩护 -
And we will never forget them.
我们永远不会忘记他们。
That doesn't mean that I want to kneel to someone who--
这并不意味着我想要跪到某个人身上 -
I swore myself and the North to her cause.
我向她自己和北方发誓。
I respect that.
我尊重。
You respect it?
你尊重吗?
We needed her.
我们需要她。
We needed her army, her dragons.
我们需要她的军队，她的龙。
You did the right thing.
你做了正确的事情。
And we're doing the right thing telling you
我们正在做正确的事告诉你
we don't trust your queen.
我们不相信你的女王。
-You don't know her yet. -I'll never know her.
- 你还不认识她 - 我永远不会认识她。
She's not one of us.
她不是我们中的一员。
If you only trust the people you grew up with,
如果你只相信你长大的人，
you won't make many allies.
你不会成为很多盟友。
That's all right.
没关系。
I don't need many allies.
我不需要很多盟友。
JON: Arya... -We're family.
JON:艾莉亚...... - 我们是一家人。
The four of us.
我们四个人
The last of the Starks.
斯塔克斯的最后一个。
I've never been a Stark.
我从未成为斯塔克。
SANSA: You are.
SANSA: 你是。
You're just as much Ned Stark's child as any of us.
你和我们任何一个人一样，和Ned Stark一样。
You're my brother.
你是我的兄弟。
Not my half-brother or my bastard brother.
不是我的同父异母兄弟或我的私生子兄弟。
My brother.
我的兄弟。
It's your choice.
这是你的选择。
I need to tell you something.
我要告诉你些事。
But you have to swear you'll never tell another soul.
但你必须发誓，你永远不会告诉另一个灵魂。
What is it?
它是什么?
You have to swear it, before I tell you.
你必须发誓， 在我告诉你之前
How can I promise to keep a secret
我怎么能保守秘密
if I don't even know what it is?
如果我甚至不知道它是什么?
Swear it.
发誓
I swear it.
我发誓。
Tell them.
告诉他们。
TYRION: So she's going to stay here with you?
TYRION: 所以她会和你待在一起吗?
She's sworn to protect the Stark girls, so...
她发誓要保护斯塔克女孩，所以......
Say something snide.
说点嗤之以鼻。
I'm happy.
我很高兴。
I'm happy that you're happy.
我很高兴你很高兴。
I'm happy that you'll finally have to climb for it.
我很高兴你终于要为它攀登了。
Do you know how long I've waited to tell tall-person jokes?
你知道我等了多长时间讲高人笑话吗?
-To climbing mountains.
- 爬山
To climbing mountains.
去爬山。
-What's she like down there? -What?
- 她喜欢什么? -什么?
That's not your concern.
那不是你的顾虑。
I haven't been with a woman for years.
多年来我一直没有和女人在一起。
-Give me a morsel. -You're a dog.
- 给我一点点。 - 你是一只狗
I am the Imp, and I demand to know.
我是Imp， 我要求知道。
BRONN: I knew you were fucking her.
BRONN: 我知道你他妈的。
A pair of tall, blond toffs.
一双高大的金发女郎。
Must be like looking in the mirror.
一定要像照镜子一样。
TYRION: Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
TYRION: 黑水的Ser Bronn。
Where's your drink?
你的饮料在哪里?
What are you-- What are you doing up North?
你是做什么的 - 你在北方做什么?
What are you doing with that?
你在做什么?
Oh, this?
哦，这个?
This is for you.
这个给你。
For both of you.
对你们两个。
TYRION: You're supposed to be south.
TYRION: 你应该在南方。
You boys are a pair of gold-plated cunts.
你们男孩是一对镀金色的屄。
-Do you know that? -That's a bit rude.
-你知道吗? - 有点粗鲁。
Year after year, I've shoveled Lannister shit,
一年又一年， 我把兰尼斯特的狗屎铲了一下，
-and what do I have to show? -You're a knight, thanks to me.
- 我需要展示什么? - 你是个骑士，谢谢你。
Thanks to me. And that title's worth as much
谢谢我。 这个头衔的价值也是如此
as a blond hair from your brother's ballsack.
作为你哥哥的金发发型。
Power resides where men believe--
权力存在于人们相信的地方 -
BRONN: Shut your mouth.
BRONN: 闭上你的嘴。
TYRION: I'm just trying-- -I've never hit a dwarf before,
TYRION:我只是想 - - 我以前从未打过矮人，
but say another word and I will belt you.
但是说另一个词，我会把你带走。
See, I don't believe you'd do that, after all--
毕竟，我不相信你会这样做 -
You couldn't do it on your best day,
你不能在最好的一天做到，
you one-handed fuck.
你单手他妈的。
And your best days are long gone.
而你最好的日子早已不复存在。
You broke my nose!
你弄坏了我的鼻子！
-I did not break your nose. -How do you know?
- 我没有打破你的鼻子。 -你怎么知道的?
Because I've been breaking noses since I was your size,
因为我是你的体型，所以我一直在打鼻子
and I know what it sounds like. Now listen.
而且我知道它听起来像什么。 现在听。
Your sister offered me Riverrun.
你妹妹给了我Riverrun。
Nice big castle, good lands,
漂亮的大城堡，美好的土地，
plenty of peasants who do what they're told.
有很多农民做他们所说的话。
-And you trust Cersei-- -I knew your sister was dead
- 你相信Cersei-- 我知道你姐姐死了
the second I saw those dragons.
第二次，我看到了那些龙。
Now, your army may be torn to shit,
现在， 你的军队可能会被撕成碎片，
but I'd still bet on your Dragon Queen to win.
但我仍然打赌你的龙女王要赢。
And it just so happens I'm a betting man.
事实恰恰相反，我是一个博彩人。
If Cersei's dead, she can't pay up.
如果瑟曦死了， 她付不起钱。
Mmm, that's good. Of course, the odds change
嗯，那很好。 当然，赔率变化
if the Dragon Queen's Hand turns up dead.
如果龙女王之手出现死亡。
Maybe a few of her top generals get picked off one by one.
也许她的一些高级将领一个接一个地被挑选出来。
-All of a sudden... TYRION: May I speak?
-突然间... TYRION:我可以说话吗?
Why not? Only death will shut you up.
为什么不? 只有死亡会让你闭嘴。
We made a deal long ago. Do you remember?
我们很久以前就达成了协议。 你还记得吗?
If anyone offered me money
如果有人给我钱
to kill you, you'd pay me double.
杀了你 你付我一倍。
What's double Riverrun?
什么是双Riverrun?
Highgarden.
Highgarden。
You could be Lord of the Reach.
你可能成为Reach的主宰。
-Highgarden? Are you mad? -It's better than being dead.
-Highgarden?你生气吗? - 它比死了更好。
He's not going to kill us.
他不会杀了我们。
He wouldn't be talking to us if--
如果 - 他不会和我们说话
The way I see it,
我看的方式，
I only need one of the Lannister brothers alive.
我只需要一个兰尼斯特兄弟活着。
Highgarden will never belong to a cutthroat.
高级花园永远不会属于残酷。
BRONN: No? Who were your ancestors,
BRONN: 没有?谁是你的祖先，
the ones who made your family rich?
那些让你的家庭富裕的人?
Fancy lads in silk?
丝绸中的花式小伙子?
They were fucking cutthroats.
他们是他妈的cutthroats。
That's how all the great houses started, isn't it?
这就是所有伟大的房子开始的原因，不是吗?
With a hard bastard who was good at killing people.
有一个擅长杀人的硬混蛋。
Kill a few hundred people, they make you a lord.
杀了几百人， 他们会让你成为一个领主。
Kill a few thousand, they make you king.
杀了几千， 他们让你成为国王。
And then all your cocksucking grandsons can ruin the family
然后你所有的公鸡孙子都会毁了这个家庭
with their cocksucking ways.
与他们的cocksucking方式。
Highgarden.
Highgarden。
Give me your word.
把你的话告诉我。
You have my word.
你有我的话。
None of this means a thing until we take King's Landing.
在我们夺取King's Landing之前，这些都不是意味着什么。
We ride south in the morning.
我们早上骑在南方。
We could use an officer
我们可以使用一名军官
with knowledge of the city's defenses.
了解城市的防御。
Oh, no.
不好了。
No, my fighting days are done.
不，我的战斗日子已经结束了。
But I still got a few killing days left, you hear me?
但是我还有几天被杀，你听到了吗?
I'll come find you when the war is done.
战争结束后我会来找你的。
Till then, don't die.
直到那时，不要死。
For fuck's sake.
为了他妈的缘故。
HOUND: Not anymore.
猎犬: 不再。
I don't like crowds.
我不喜欢人群。
ARYA: Me neither.
ARYA: 我也不。
HOUND: Why not? They all love you now.
猎犬: 为什么不?他们现在都爱你。
You're the big hero.
你是大英雄。
Don't like heroes.
不喜欢英雄。
It must have felt good sticking a knife in that horned fucker.
在那个有角的笨蛋中，一定感觉很好。
Felt better than dying.
感觉比死亡更好。
You're heading to King's Landing?
你要去King's Landing吗?
I have some unfinished business.
我有一些未完成的事情。
Me too.
我也是。
I don't plan on coming back.
我不打算回来。
Neither do I.
我也不。
Gonna leave me to die again if I get hurt?
如果我受伤，会让我再次死吗?
Probably.
大概。
My lady.
我的女士。
"My lord" is the standard response.
“我的君主” 是标准的回应。
Why her?
为什么她?
TYRION: You know she loves your brother.
TYRION: 你知道她爱你的兄弟。
That doesn't mean she'll be a good queen.
这并不意味着她会成为一个好女王。
You seem determined to dislike her.
你似乎决定不喜欢她。
A good relationship
良好的关系
between the Iron Throne and the North
在铁王座和北方之间
has been the core of every peaceful,
一直是每个和平的核心，
prosperous reign we've ever known.
我们所知道的繁荣统治。
Jon will be Warden of the North,
乔恩将成为北方的守望者，
so a good relationship seems likely.
所以很可能会建立良好的关系。
I don't expect him to spend much time here going forward.
我不指望他在这里花很多时间。
Well, I suppose that's up to him.
好， 我想这取决于他。
Sansa, look at me.
Sansa，看着我。
With Jon in the capital,
乔恩在首都，
you'll be the true power in the North.
你将成为北方的真正力量。
I'd feel much better about the future
我对未来感觉好多了
if I left here today believing
如果我今天离开这里相信
that you and Daenerys were allies.
你和丹妮莉丝是盟友。
What are you worried about? Jon's taking our army with him.
你在担心什么? 乔恩带着我的军队。
Your queen still has her dragons--
你的女王还有她的龙 -
She's your queen too.
她也是你的女王。
You don't have to be her friend.
你不必是她的朋友。
But why provoke her?
但为什么要挑衅她?
How is that in the best interest of your family,
这对你的家人有什么好处，
-or the North, or--? -You're afraid of her.
- 或北方，或 - ? - 你害怕她
Every good ruler needs to inspire a bit of fear.
每个好的统治者都需要激发一点恐惧。
I don't want Jon to go down there.
我不希望乔恩去那里。
The men in my family don't do well in the capital.
我家里的男人在首都表现不佳。
No, but as your brother once told me,
不，但正如你的兄弟曾告诉我的，
he's not a Stark.
他不是斯塔克。
Are you all right?
你没事儿吧?
Her people love her, you've seen that.
她的人爱她， 你已经看到了。
You've seen how they fight for her.
你已经看到他们如何为她而战。
She wants to make the world a better place.
她想让世界变得更美好。
I believe in her.
我相信她。
Tyrion.
提利昂。
What if there's someone else?
如果有其他人怎么办?
Someone better?
有人更好吗?
You're not gonna ride the dragon south?
你不会骑龙南?
Just a horse.
只是一匹马。
Rhaegal needs to heal.
Rhaegal需要愈合。
He doesn't need me weighing him down.
他不需要我压低他。
You weigh as much as two fleas fucking.
你的体重高达两只跳蚤他妈的。
I'm taking the Free Folk home.
我正在参加免费民俗之家。
We've had enough of the south.
我们已经受够了南方。
The women down here don't like me.
这里的女人不喜欢我。
This is the North, you know.
你知道，这是北方。
And the Free Folk are welcome to stay.
欢迎自由民谣留下来。
It isn't home.
它不在家。
We need room to wander.
我们需要徘徊的空间。
I'll take them back through Castle Black
我会带他们回到布莱克城堡
as soon as the winter storms pass.
一旦冬季风暴过去。
Back where we belong.
回到我们所属的地方。
It's where he belongs too.
这也是他所属的地方。
A direwolf has no place in the south.
一只猎狼在南方没有地方。
Will you take him with you?
你带他去吗?
He'll be happier up there.
他会在那里更快乐。
So would you.
你也愿意吗?
I wish I was going with you.
我希望我和你一起去。
This is farewell, then.
这是告别。
You never know.
你永远都不会知道。
You've got the North in you.
你在北方有你。
The real North.
真正的北方。
Yes, well, the nights have been getting longer
是的，嗯，夜晚变得越来越长
and there wasn't that much to do in Oldtown.
在Oldtown没有那么多事要做。
There's only so many books a person can read, so we--
一个人只能读这么多书，所以我们 -
I'm sure he knows how it happens, Sam.
我确定他知道这是怎么回事，Sam。
If it's a boy, we want to name him Jon.
如果是男孩， 我们想把他命名为Jon。
I hope it's a girl.
我希望这是一个女孩。
You're the best friend I ever had.
你是我曾经拥有的最好的朋友。
You too, Sam.
你也是，山姆。
TYRION: Think of the past 20 years.
TYRION: 想想过去20年。
The war, the murder, the misery.
战争，谋杀，痛苦。
All of it because Robert Baratheon loved someone
所有这一切都因为Robert Baratheon爱一个人
who didn't love him back.
谁不爱他回来。
How many others know?
有多少人知道?
Including us? Eight.
包括我们?八。
Well, then it's not a secret anymore.
好吧，那不再是秘密了。
It's information.
这是信息。
If a handful of people know now, hundreds will know soon.
如果现在有少数人知道， 数百人很快就会知道。
Then what happens?
然后会发生什么?
She loses the North.
她失去了北方。
She loses the Vale, Sansa will make sure of that.
她失去了淡水河谷， Sansa将确保这一点。
No, it's worse than that.
不，这比那更糟糕。
He has the better claim to the throne.
他对王位的要求更高。
He doesn't want the throne.
他不想要王位。
I'm not sure it matters what he wants.
我不确定他想要什么。
The fact is, people are drawn to him.
事实上， 人们被他吸引。
Wildlings, Northmen.
Wildlings，Northmen。
He's a war hero.
他是战争英雄。
He loves our queen.
他爱我们的女王。
And she loves him.
她爱他。
If we marry them, they could rule together.
如果我们嫁给他们， 他们可以一起统治。
She's his aunt.
她是他的阿姨。
That never stopped a Targaryen before.
那之前从未停止过Targaryen。
No, but Jon grew up in Winterfell.
不，但Jon在Winterfell长大。
Is marrying your aunt common in the North?
嫁给你在北方常见的阿姨?
You know our queen better than I do.
你比我更了解我们的女王。
Do you think she wants to share the throne?
你认为她想分享宝座吗?
She does not like to have her authority questioned.
她不喜欢对她的权威提出质疑。
Something she has in common
她有一个共同点
with every monarch who ever lived.
与每一位曾经生活过的君主在一起。
I worry about her state of mind.
我担心她的心态。
We are advisors to the queen.
我们是女王的顾问。
Worrying about her state of mind is our job.
担心她的心态是我们的工作。
We still have to take King's Landing.
我们仍然需要采取国王登陆。
Maybe Cersei will win and kill us all.
也许Cersei会赢得并杀死我们所有人。
That would solve our problems.
这将解决我们的问题。
Get to the skiff. Now!
去小船。现在！
SOLDIER 1: Spears!
士兵1: 布兰妮！
SOLDIER 2: They're coming round again!
士兵2: 他们又来了！
SOLDIER 3: Go!
士兵3: 走！
SOLDIER 4: Clear!
士兵4: 明确！
SOLDIER 5: Man your stations!
士兵5: 男人你的车站！
MISSANDEI: No!
MISSANDEI:不！
SOLDIER 4: Go! Go! SOLDIER 5: Clear!
士兵4:去！走！ 士兵5:清楚！
Missandei?
Missandei?
Missandei!
Missandei！
CERSEI: Our message was well-received, then?
瑟曦: 我们的信息很受欢迎， 然后?
QYBURN: Your people have heard the Usurper is coming.
QYBURN: 你的人民听说过篡位者的到来。
They are grateful for your protection
他们感谢您的保护
within the walls of the Red Keep.
在红色保持的墙壁内。
You're certain about the dragon?
你肯定龙?
I saw it sink beneath the waves.
我看到它沉入海浪之下。
That must have been glorious.
那肯定是光荣的。
The glory is yours, my queen.
荣耀是你的，我的女王。
When the war is won, the Lion shall rule the land,
战争胜利时， 狮子将统治这片土地，
the Kraken shall rule the sea...
海妖统治大海......
and our child shall one day rule them all.
我们的孩子有一天会统治他们。
She's coming for you.
她来找你。
Of course she is.
她当然是。
Keep the gates open.
打开大门。
If she wants to take the castle, she'll have to murder
如果她想要占领城堡， 她必须谋杀
thousands of innocent people first.
成千上万无辜的人。
So much for "the Breaker of Chains."
对于“链条断路器”这么多。
GREY WORM: We will storm the city, my queen.
灰色的蠕虫: 我们将风暴城市， 我的女王。
We will kill your enemies. All of them.
我们会杀死你的敌人。 他们都是。
VARYS: Your Grace.
瓦里斯: 你的恩典。
I promised you I would look you in the eye and speak directly
我答应过你，我会看着你，直接说话
if I ever thought you were making a mistake.
如果我以为你犯了错误
This is a mistake.
这是个错误。
You saw my child fall from the sky.
你看到我的孩子从天而降。
They took Missandei.
他们带走了Missandei。
VARYS: Cersei needs to be destroyed,
瓦里斯: Cersei需要被摧毁，
but if we attack King's Landing with Drogon and the Unsullied
但是如果我们用Drogon和Unsullied攻击King's Landing
and the Dothraki,
还有Dothraki，
tens of thousands of innocents will die.
成千上万的无辜者将死去。
That is why Cersei is bringing them into the Red Keep.
这就是Cersei将他们带入Red Keep的原因。
These are the people you came here to protect.
这些是你来这里保护的人。
I beg you, Your Grace.
求求你，你的恩典。
Do not destroy the city you came to save.
不要破坏你来拯救的城市。
Do not become what you have always struggled to defeat.
不要成为你一直在努力打败的东西。
Do you believe we're here for a reason, Lord Varys?
瓦里斯勋爵，你相信我们在这里是有原因的吗?
I'm here to free the world from tyrants.
我来这里是为了让世界摆脱暴君。
That is my destiny...
那是我的命运......
and I will serve it, no matter the cost.
我会为它服务， 无论成本如何。
It could be a fortnight before Jon and the allied armies
在乔恩和盟军之前可能还需要两周时间
make it to King's Landing.
进入King's Landing。
In the meantime, demand Cersei surrender.
同时， 要求瑟曦投降。
Offer her her life in exchange for the throne.
以王位换取她的生命。
If there's a chance to avoid the coming slaughter,
如果有机会避免即将到来的屠杀，
we should make the effort.
我们应该努力。
Speaking to Cersei will not prevent a slaughter.
对Cersei说话不会阻止屠杀。
But perhaps it's good the people see
但也许人们看到的很好
that Daenerys Stormborn made every effort to avoid bloodshed,
Daenerys Stormborn尽一切努力避免流血事件，
and Cersei Lannister refused.
和Cersei Lannister拒绝了。
They should know whom to blame
他们应该知道应该责怪谁
when the sky falls down upon them.
当天空落在他们身上。
I've served tyrants most of my life.
我大部分时间都在为暴君服务。
They all talk about destiny.
他们都在谈论命运。
She's a girl who walked into a fire with three stones
她是一个用三块石头走进火炉的女孩
and walked out with three dragons.
然后走了三条龙。
How could she not believe in destiny?
她怎么不相信命运?
Perhaps that's the problem.
也许这就是问题所在。
Her life has convinced her
她的生活使她信服
that she was sent here to save us all.
她被派到这里救我们所有人。
And how do you know she wasn't?
你怎么知道她不是?
Then there's the problem of Jon Snow.
然后是Jon Snow的问题。
Perhaps it's actually a solution.
也许它实际上是一种解决方案。
You know them both.
你们都知道。
Tell me, who do you think would make a better ruler?
告诉我，你认为谁会成为更好的统治者?
He doesn't want the throne.
他不想要王位。
That's why he bent the knee.
这就是他弯曲膝盖的原因。
Have you considered the best ruler
你认为最好的统治者了吗?
might be someone who doesn't want to rule?
可能是一个不想统治的人?
We're discussing treason.
我们正在讨论叛国罪。
Don't pretend you haven't thought about it.
不要假装你没有想过它。
Of course I've thought about it. Thoughts aren't treason.
当然我已经考虑过了。 思想不是叛国罪。
He's temperate and measured. He's a man,
他很温和而且很有考验。 他是个男人，
which makes him more appealing to the lords of Westeros,
这让他对维斯特洛的领主更有吸引力，
whose support we are going to need.
我们将需要他们的支持。
Joffrey was a man.
乔佛里是个男人。
I don't think a cock is a true qualification,
我不认为公鸡是真正的资格，
as I'm sure you'd agree.
因为我相信你会同意的。
And he's the heir to the throne.
他是王位的继承人。
Yes, because he's a man. Cocks are important, I'm afraid.
是的，因为他是个男人。 我担心，公鸡很重要。
What about my earlier proposal?
我早先的建议怎么样?
They could rule together as king and queen.
他们可以作为国王和王后一起统治。
She's too strong for him.
她对他来说太强大了。
She'd bend him to her will, as she already has.
她会弯曲他的意志， 因为她已经有了。
He could temper her worst impulses.
他可以缓和她最糟糕的冲动。
As you have?
你有吗?
You're drinking quite a lot.
你喝的很多。
A Targaryen father and a Stark mother.
Targaryen父亲和Stark母亲。
Jon's the one man alive who might actually be able
乔恩是一个活着的人，实际上可能
to keep the North in the Seven Kingdoms.
保持北方七国。
How many kings and queens have you served?
你有多少国王和王后?
Five? Six? I've lost count.
五?六?我已经数不清了。
-You've always known my reasons. -At a certain point,
- 你总是知道我的理由。 - 在某一点上，
you choose a person you believe in,
你选择一个你相信的人，
and you fight for that person.
你为那个人而战
Even if you know it's a mistake?
即使你知道这是一个错误?
I believe in our queen.
我相信我们的女王。
She'll make the right choice.
她会做出正确的选择。
With the help of her loyal advisors.
在她的忠实顾问的帮助下。
You know where my loyalty stands.
你知道我的忠诚在哪里。
You know I will never betray the realm.
你知道我永远不会背叛这个领域。
What is the realm?
这个领域是什么?
A vast continent, home to millions of people,
广阔的大陆， 数百万人的家，
most of whom don't care who sits on the Iron Throne.
大多数人并不关心谁坐在铁王座上。
Millions of people, many of whom will die
人山人海， 他们中的许多人会死
if the wrong person sits on that throne.
如果错误的人坐在那个宝座上
We don't know their names,
我们不知道他们的名字，
but they're just as real as you and I.
但他们和你我一样真实。
They deserve to live.
他们应该活下去。
They deserve food for their children.
他们应该为孩子们提供食物。
I will act in their interest, no matter the personal cost.
我会按照他们的利益行事， 无论个人成本如何。
So, what happens to her?
那么，她怎么了?
Please.
请。
Don't.
别。
I've spoken as honestly as I can.
我尽可能诚实地说话。
Each of us has a choice to make.
我们每个人都可以选择。
I pray we choose wisely.
我祈祷我们明智地选择。
MAN 1: I'm just about to start it.
男人1: 我即将开始。
WOMAN 1: Good luck.
女人1: 祝好运。
MAN 2: Protect shell right up to the wall.
男人2: 保护外壳直到墙壁。
MAN 1: All right, I'll put another one on it.
男人1: 行， 我会另外放一个。
MAN 3: He's headed down to the cellar.
男人3: 他正走向地窖。
I'll need a cart over here.
我需要一辆车在这里。
MAN 4: That's it, thanks.
男人4: 就是这样，谢谢。
Thank you.
谢谢。
WOMAN 2: It's really heavy, mind you.
女人2: 请注意，这真的太重了。
MAN 5: We need some more water.
男人5: 我们需要更多的水。
MAN 3: Take it down there!
男人3: 把它拿下来！
...as are the rest of her advisors.
......和她的其他顾问一样。
What happened?
发生了什么?
Euron Greyjoy ambushed Queen Daenerys and her fleet.
Euron Greyjoy伏击了女王丹妮莉丝和她的舰队。
One of the dragons was killed, several ships destroyed,
其中一条龙被杀， 几艘船被摧毁，
Missandei captured.
米桑迪被捕。
I always wanted to be there when they execute your sister.
当他们执行你的妹妹时，我一直想去那儿。
Seems like I won't get the chance.
好像我不会有机会。
They're going to destroy that city.
他们要毁掉那个城市。
You know they will.
你知道他们会。
JAIME: Have you ever run away from a fight?
JAIME: 你有没有逃避战斗?
You're not like your sister. You're not.
你不喜欢你的妹妹。 你不是。
You're better than she is.
你比她好。
You're a good man and you can't save her.
你是一个好人，你无法拯救她。
You don't need to die with her.
你不需要和她一起死。
Stay here.
留在这儿。
Stay with me.
跟我在一起。
Please.
请。
Stay.
留。
You think I'm a good man?
你觉得我是个好人吗?
I pushed a boy out a tower window,
我把一个男孩推到了一个塔窗外，
crippled him for life
使他残废了一辈子
for Cersei.
对于瑟曦。
I strangled my cousin with my own hands
我用自己的双手勒死了表弟
just to get back to Cersei.
只是为了回到瑟曦。
I would have murdered
我会谋杀
every man, woman and child in Riverrun
Riverrun的每个男人，女人和孩子
for Cersei.
对于瑟曦。
She's hateful.
她很讨厌。
And so am I.
我也是。
My lord.
我的君主。
Queen Daenerys demands Cersei's unconditional surrender
女王丹妮莉丝要求Cersei无条件投降
and the immediate release of Missandei of Naath.
和Naath的Missandei立即释放。
Queen Cersei demands Daenerys's unconditional surrender.
女王瑟曦要求丹妮莉丝无条件投降。
If she refuses, Missandei of Naath will die here and now.
如果她拒绝，Naath的Missandei将在这里和现在死去。
Qyburn...
Qyburn ...
you're a rational man.
你是一个理性的人。
Or so I flatter myself, my lord.
或者我自以为是 我的君主。 我们有机会， 也许是我们最后的机会 避免大屠杀 是。
Help me.
帮我。
I don't want to see this city burn.
我不想看到这个城市燃烧。
I don't want to hear the screams of children burning alive.
我不想听到孩子们活着烧的尖叫声。
No, it is not a pleasant sound.
不，这不是一个愉快的声音。
Help me save this city.
帮我救这个城市。
My lord, I am only a mouthpiece for our queen.
我的主人，我只是我们女王的喉舌。
TYRION: Your queen.
TYRION: 你的女王。
Cersei is Queen of the Seven Kingdoms.
瑟曦是七国女王。
You are her subject.
你是她的主题。
Her reign is over.
她的统治结束了。
You understand this. Help her understand it.
你明白这一点。 帮助她了解它。
We understand nothing of the sort.
我们什么都不懂。
Your queen's last dragon is vulnerable.
你女王的最后一条龙很脆弱。
Your armies are battle-weary and depleted,
你的军队疲惫不堪，疲惫不堪，
while ours have been reinforced with the Golden Compan--
虽然我们的黄金公司得到了加强 -
CAPTAIN: Ready!
队长: 准备！
Nock!
诺克！
Draw!
画！
I know you don't care about your people.
我知道你不关心你的人。
Why should you?
你为什么要?
They hate you and you hate them.
他们恨你，你讨厌他们。
But you're not a monster.
但你不是怪物。
I know this.
我知道这个。
I know this because I've seen it.
我知道这是因为我见过它。
You've always loved your children.
你一直都爱你的孩子。
More than yourself,
比你自己更多
more than Jaime...
超过Jaime ......
more than anything.
比什么都重要。
I beg you.
我求求你。
If not for yourself, then for your child.
如果不适合自己， 然后为你的孩子。
Your reign is over,
你的统治结束了，
but that doesn't mean your life has to end.
但这并不意味着你的生活必须结束。
It doesn't mean your baby has to die.
这并不意味着你的宝宝必须死。
If you have any last words, now is the time.
如果你有任何遗言， 现在是时候了。
Dracarys.
Dracarys。
No.
没有。
? (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ?
?(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)?
(CLOCK TICKING)
(时钟收费)
(TICKING INTENSIFIES)
(强调强化)
? (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ?
?(音乐强化)?
? (MUSIC STOPS) ?
?(音乐商店)?
? (MUSIC CONTINUES) ?
?(音乐继续)?